http://www.redington.com/privacy-policy

RodsReelsCombosWadingApparelAccessoriesCollectionsGift CardsGift GuideSaleNew to Fly?VideosStoriesSearch0Free ground shipping on all orders through the holidaysSearchSHOPEXPERIENCERodsReelsCombosWadingApparelAccessoriesCollectionsGift CardsGift GuideSaleNew to Fly?VideosStoriesMy AcountForgot Password?New AccountGOFind a storeCustomer ServiceOrder StatusRepairsCareersContact UsSubscribe to our newsletterPrivacy PolicyYour privacy is important to us and we are committed to protecting it. Any information you provide us is kept completely confidential and will not be used without your consent.Email Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy applies to email addresses submitted for the purposes of subscribing to Redington’s e-mail newsletters offered through Redington.com.Your submission of an email address signifies your acceptance of email messages from Redington - primarily, the e-mail newsletters that you have signed up to receive. Periodically, Redington sends promotional email messages about products and promotions offered by Redington to its e-mail newsletters subscribers and dealer base.You can opt out of email messages from Redington at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of all email messages.Disclosure of InformationWe do not sell, rent, or loan your information to third parties without your permission. So, for example, we do not sell your email address or other information to mass marketers.Information We CollectLike many other websites, Redington uses a standard technology called "cookies". Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive and not on our site. They can help make your Internet experience quicker and more convenient. Cookies allow you to keep shopping cart information independent from our servers. Cookies help us understand how customers use the service, which allows us to improve and tailor the service.Third paties (such as AdRoll) may place cookies on your browser for targeted advertising purposes. Your personal data is collected such as IP addresses, cookie identifiers or other tracking technologies such as pixels and end-user website activity. But we will never sell your information to third parties. Learn more on AdRoll's Privacy Policy.Check who delivers tailored online ads and your choices to opt-out of receiving them www.networkadvertising.org and www.youronlinechoices.com (Europe only).Privacy Protection for ChildrenIn compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), we will not knowingly provide our service to persons under the age of 18
